# JOE JORDAN

#### Junior full-stack web developer

with strong creative problemsolving skills and attention to detail. Years of experience as a teacher and set builder translates to ability to work with designers and teams, meet deadlines, and deliver a usable, high-quality product.

# TOOLS & SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
- Node.js, Express, MongoDB
- · React, Angular
- · React Native
- Jest, Cucumber, Puppeteer
- Responsive design
- Writing/editing/research
- Trained in communication

## STRENGTHS

- Diligent and personable
- Creative problem-solver
- Expertise in hearing and addressing client concerns
- Committed to promoting a safe and enjoyable work environment

# EDUCATION

2022 • CareerFoundry Full-Stack Immersion Program

Intensive, mentored, project-based online training program in contemporary full-stack web development

2014 • Texas Region 10 ESC Teacher Certification, ELAR 8-12

Nationally recognized certification program for post-graduate teacher training

1994 • UC Santa Barbara Bachelor of Arts, English

Comprehensive liberal arts education with a focus on English literature

- <u>lankyjoe.com</u>
- github.com/shplank
- in linkedin.com/in/lankyjoe

## WORK EXPERIENCE

# Theater Operations Specialist

CSU Dominguez Hills | Carson, CA | 2019-present

- Liasing with faculty, staff, and clients to schedule and facilitate events and productions
- Interpreting and realizing complex theatrical designs for each of the university's seasonal productions
- Supervising and training dozens of student workers in carpentry skills and safe building protocols
- Improving organization and maintenance procedures for large, busy shop facility and theater space

#### **Technical Director**

Sacred Fools Theater Company | Los Angeles, CA | 2017-18

- Established positive, supportive client experiences for high-volume theater complex
- Created user-friendly technical environment for both clients and in-house technicians
- Trained and assisted staff and clients in various theater technical capacities
- Worked closely with dozens of technicians to execute designs to the highest standards of safety and artistry

## **English Teacher**

Bonham High School | Bonham, TX | 2014-17

- Provided rigorous, standards-based instruction to previously underserved community
- Raised students' standardized test scores by 12% on average as well as overall passing and graduation rates
- Elevated school's profile by coaching academic teams to regional victories
- Fostered inclusive learning environment for all students and advised school's first Gay-Straight Alliance program

References available upon request.